Guide to the Stanley Hanna papers SC1256
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2015-112
  - Research and files
    - Intermediate Structure in the Giant El Resonance in the 19F (p,Ƴ) 20Ne Reactions. Calarco, Kurjan, Fisher, S.S. Hanna Phys. Lett. 92B, 67, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Res Fluorescence, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Computation Book Preston and Hanna Course Positrons, Polarization, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - "Giant Mulitpole Resonances", S.S. Hanna Dubna, 1976 Jun (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Polarized Radioactive Beams Stanley S. Hanna Triumf, 1985 Sep (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Polarization in Nuclear Physics S.S. Hanna Florence, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Current developments in giant resonances - S.S. Hanna; Conf. proceedings Leuven, Belgium, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Survey of E2 Strength Observed in Capture Reactions" S.S. Hanna Poland, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Absolute cross section for the reaction H(p,Ƴ) measurements. Calarco, Hanna, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "Decay of Giant Resonances", S.S. Hanna Osaka Conference (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - FAS (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Oxford Trip (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Jobs- terminated + answered, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Positrons (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Positrons (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Positrons (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Mossbauer letters (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Mossbauer papers (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Mossbauer papers (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Giant Resonances (S.S. Hanna) Comm. Nucl. Part. Phys. 11, 79, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Analysis of the Magnetic Moments of Mirror Nuclei S.S. Hanna, J.W. Hugg (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Post Doctoral Applicants, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - W. Rambler, R. Preston (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Mossbauer Effect Data Index Issue 2 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Mossbauer Effect Data Index Issue 1 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Mossbuaer Effect (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Mossbauer Effect Literature (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, memos (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - unlabeled (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Goldring, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Preprints to Send (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - 3He Target and Cryostat (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Li7 - Be7 Lifetimes (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Kuan (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - AIP committee (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - ROAF (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Mechanics notes (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Indiana workshop, 1983 Jun (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Astronomy papers (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - infra-red (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Chemistry, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - battlefields (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Hanna (Invited talk) ICPR, Asilomar, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Hasinoff, Fisher and Hanna Nuclear Physics, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Glavish, Avida, Hanna, Diener, Boyd, Chang Phys. Rev. Lett., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Russell, Latshaw and Hanna and Kainal Nuclear Physics, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - O'Connell, Latshaw, Black and Hanna ICPR, Asilomar, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Minamisono, Hugg, Mavis, Saylor, Lazarus, Glavish, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Ceperly, Sokolowski, Ben-zvi, Glavish, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Interaction sizes of the Even Neodymium Isotopes.. S. L. Tabor, B. A. Watson, S. S. Hanna, 1976 Aug (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Minamisono, Hugg, Hall, Mavis, Glavish, 1976 Jul (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Phy. Rev. C, G. Langouche, N. S. Dixon, Y. Mahmud, B. B. Triplett S. S. Hanna, Mag. Moment of the 1st excited state of 121Sb…, 1976 Jun (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Minamisono, Hugg, Mavis, Saylor, Glavish, 1976 Mar (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Fiarman, 1975 Oct (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Boolchand, Tenhover, Jha, Langouche, Triplett, 1975 Sep (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - McGraw-Hill Encycl. Of Science and Tech. 4th Ed., Vol. 9 p. 227A. "Giant Nuclear Resonances," Hanna, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Minamisono, Hugg, Mavis, Saylor, Lazarus, Glavish, Hanna; Phys. Review Letters, 1975 Jun (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ceperley, Ben-Zvi, Glavish, 1975 Jun (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Mahmud, Boolchand, Hanna, Triplett; Journal de Physique, "Mossbauer Effect Studies of Te Cmpds", 1974 Dec (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Notebook (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - documents (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Physcial Review C E1 and E2 strength, 1979 Jul (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Tabor, Watson, 1975 Jan (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Kuhlmann, Ventura, Calarco, Mavis, 1975 May (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Giant E1 Resonances in 8Be from the Reaction 7Li… G.A. Fisher, P. Paul, F. Riess, S.S. Hanna, 1976 Jul (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Langouche, Dixon, Gettner, and Hanna Journal de Physique, 1980 Jan (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Langouche, Triplett, Dixon, Mahmud, 1977 Mar (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Optics, Book Review: Mossbauer Spectroscopy, Gonzer- S.S. Hanna, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Nuclear Orientation of 125Sb in Pd2MnSb… G. Langouche, B.B. Triplett, N.S. Dixon, SSH, 1977 Mar (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Hanna Ann. Of the Israel Phys. Soc., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Boolchand, Tenhover, Jha, Langouche, Triplett, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Minamisono, Hugg, Hall, Mavis, Clark, 1976 Dec (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Program Comm (Fisher) (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Tandem Schedules (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Tritium Gas CRA (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - LASL Notes (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Australian Conf (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Mass 10 Paper 13 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Preprint List (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Spires (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Customs, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - laboratory notebook (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Structure of Low-Medium mass nuclei, 1964 Mar 5-6 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Progress Intermediate Energy and Nuclear Physics Laboratory, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - E2 Theory and General (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Stanley Hanna (Physics 83Q) 298 The Physics of Terrorist Bomb Detention (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Physics 23, Electricity and Optics S.S. Hanna, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Hanna Classwork Information Physics 200-203 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Physics 11. World of Physics S.S. Hanna, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Department 70-71 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Conference, 1970 Sep (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Gunn (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - LAMPF Closing Talk - transparencies (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Tables for the Transformation of Angular Distribution Data from the Laboratory System to the Center of Mass System, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Symposium in Honor of D. Allan Bromley, 1987 Aug 8 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Polarized Gas Jets in Crossed Beam Expt S.S. Hanna, Ohio Conference (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - On-Line Implantation of Nuclei, S.S. Hanna, Ohio Conference (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - International Conference on Nuclear Physics Amsterdam, 1982 Aug-Sep (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Proton Decay of Giant Resonances Excited By Electron Scattering" S.S. Hanna, G.E. Dodge, B.H. King, S.E. Kuhn, et al, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Polarized Radioactive Beams Stanley S. Hanna Triumf, 1985 Sep (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Nuclear Polarization in Related and Applied Fields", Stanley S. Hanna Polarization Phenomena conference in Osaka, Japan, 1985 Aug 26-30 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Gas Jet Targets Unpolarized and Polarized S.S. Hanna, CEBAF Summer Study, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Progress Report Nuclear Structure Investigations with an FN Tandem Accelerator, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Torizuka material S.S. Hanna (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Electric quadrupole strength in 20Ne… T.R. Wang et al. Hanna, 1987 Jun (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "Magnetic Moments of the first Excited 2+ States of the even-even Te isotopes" by J.S. Dunham, R.T. Westervelt, R. Avida, S.S. Hanna (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - F16 For E=118 MeU (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Nuclear Polarization in Related and Applied Fields" S.S. Hanna (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "Magnetic Moments, Polarization, and Lifetimes by Recoil Implantation," by S. Hanna, G. M. Kalvius, G. D. Sprouse, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - "The Giant Dipole Resonance in 16O Observed with the Polarized Proton Capture Reaction," Hanna, Glavish, Diener, Calarco, Chang, Avida and Boyd, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Hall, Clark, Freedman, 1988 Jan (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Giant Dipole Resonances in 12C observed with the Polarized Proton Capture Reaction, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "Study of the Giant Resonance with Polarized and Unpolarized (p,Ƴ) Reactions", S.S. HNN Sendai, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - "On the Area Analysis of Neutron and Mossbauer Resonances," by S.S. Malik and S.S. Hanna, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - "Lifetime of the First Excited State of 11Be", by S.S. Hanna, K. Nagatani, W.R. Harris, and J.W. Olness, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Jerry's project (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - IDA (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Coin Exp (e, ep) vugraphs (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "New Uses of Polarized Beams," S.S. Hanna. Preprints submitted to IEEE (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Summary of the Nuclear Physics tandem Program at Stanford (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Strong E1 Transitions in 9Be, 11Be and 13C (D.J. Millener, J.W. Olnes, E.K. Warburton and S.S. Hanna) (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - to publish? (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Reprints (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Reprints (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - correspondence, 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Data (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Reprints (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Reprints (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - correspondence (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - data, graphs (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Printed matter (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - notes, paper (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Slides, transparencies (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Papers (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - CG Coeff binder contents (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - unlabeled (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - reprints (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Abstract submitted (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Reprints (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Reprints (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Reprints (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - E2 isovector (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 16O: E2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - E1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Instrumentation, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Addresses, etc, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - NRC, 1489-1498 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - unlabeled (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 5433 S. Hanna B-decay (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 58Ni GQR (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - EO (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Higher multipoles (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - E2 splitting (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - E2: 208Pb (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - 208Pb- misc (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Vugraphs- poltargets-Zurich Ƴ rays (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - MI States (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - E2 ɑ2 strength (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - unlabeled (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Reprints, publications, paper (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Book of abstracts Topical conference on Giant Resonances, 1998 May 11-16 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - graphs (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - publications, paper (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - publications, paper (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - GR decay folder contents (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Publications (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - 21st Century Science, 1993 Sep (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - reprints, publications (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence re. tandem funding Crisis, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Funds from Univ. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1181 LAMPF (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - reprints, publications (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - S.S. Hanna reprints, publications (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Publications, reprints (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Ƴ ray absorption (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Publications/reprints (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - A Pictoral History of Los Alamos County Remember When?, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Sospin-Moscow (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Misc (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 16O: E1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 19F(p,8)20Ne (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 90Zr E1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Vu Graphs- 3H(p,Ƴ) -Delhi (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - VuGraphs -ɑ scattering - Cracow (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - S.S. Hanna, Feldman, Suffert, Kurath High Lying O+ and 3- Levels in 12C Phys. Rev. C, 1982 Mar (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Cincinnati, etc (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Polarization - Florence (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Pol targets, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Dallas talk (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Dallas talk (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous not GR (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Vu graphs - misc (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - GR talk (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - GDR: elementary A=13 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Analog GR's (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Physics 201 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Publications/reprints (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Nuclear Physics News (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - blank paper (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1981 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - hand written notes (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - forms (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - news clips, paper (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Proceedings Conference on the Utilization of Multiparameter Analyzers in Nuclear Physics, 1962 Nov 12-15 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Abstracts of Contributed papers, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - International Conference on Lattice Dynamics, 1963 Aug 5-9 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Abstracts of Contributed papers, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Electromagnetic Lifetimes and Properties of Nuclear States, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Lifetimes and Magnetic moments of States of 16N and 22Na: The recoil-into-vacuum method, 1984 Oct (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - blank paper blots (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Binder contents (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - International Journal of Theoretical Physics, 1994 Nov (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Excursion, 1987 May-Jun (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Committee on Commercial Aviation Security, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Alexander von Humboldt, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Publications (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Hand-written notes, data, calculations (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Publications (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Publications (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - unlabeled (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - publication, reprint (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Publications, reprints (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The University of Texas at Dallas Center for Quantum Electronics The Gamma-Ray Laser Project Quarterly Report, 1988 Oct - Dec (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - The University of Texas at Dallas Center for Quantum Electronics The Gamma-Ray Laser Project Quarterly Report, 1987 Oct - Dec (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - The Center for Quantum Electronics The Gamma Ray Laser Project, 1987 Jan-Mar (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - The University of Texas at Dallas Center for Quantum Electronics The Gamma-Ray Laser Project Quarterly Report, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - LBL Research Review The Keck Telescope: Mirroring the Universe, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Publications, reprints (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - News prints, 1967-1998 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - notes, data, graphs (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1998 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - course evaluations (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Chinese-translated book (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - PSI Scientific Report, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Proposal #90006 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Proposal #90007 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Graphs (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Publications, reprints (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Publications, reprints (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Magazines, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Audiovisual materials
    - Thermal Neutron Analysis Explosive Detection Systems Science Applications International Corporation, 1990; 16_1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
    - PFNA Technology, 1997 Jan; 16_2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
    - Dealing with Letter Bombs Securesearch Inc, 1992; 16_3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
    - Nova: Terrorist world trade bldg Oklahoma City, 16_4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
    - SAIC PFNA: Pulsed Fast Neutron Analysis (for searching trucks), 1992; 16_5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
    - TWA: Final FBI report, 1997 Fall; 16_6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
    - TWA 800, 1996-1997; 16_7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Computer media
    - unlabeled, 16_8; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - unlabeled, 16_9; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - unlabeled, 16_10; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - unlabeled, 16_11; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MacDraw II (Part 1) "Drawing stuff II", 1989 Jun; 16_12; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MacDraw II (part) "Drawinf Stuff III", 1989 Jun; 16_13; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MacDraft MacPaint/draw superpaint, mini draw Part McDraw II "drawing stuff I", 1988-1989 Jun; 16_14; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Paste-ease TM, 1988 Aug; 16_15; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Paste-ease II, 16_16; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - unlabeled, 16_17; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Turbo mouse dupl., 16_18; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Desk Express various vaccines, 16_19; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - old, reuse, 16_20; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - "Virus" finder, etc, 16_21; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Day Timer address/phone directry, 16_22; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - File pro Addresses BU, 16_23; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - System II Lasewriter stuff + other printer stuff etc., 16_24; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Fonts, etc, 16_25; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MacMH custom data MacSamson, 3.0 prefere MacTCP Mac TCP prep, 16_26; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - System I System 6.02 Finder etc, 16_27; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - System III Pyro, etc, 1989 Jan 5; 16_28; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Laserwriter system - 7 print monitor laser prep laser writer substitute for your current laserwriter system, 16_29; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - System 6.0.3 SUM tune-up Font WA mover finder, 1990 Apr 17; 16_30; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Terminal term_data Versaterm, versaterm Pro, VT pro_Macros, 16_31; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Printer drivers, switcher, mac eqn, laserwriter fonts, copy II Mac TM disk, Expressionist, 16_32; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Bitnet, etc, 16_33; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MS Word 4.0 utilities 1, 1989 Jul; 16_34; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MS Word 4.0 utilities 2, 16_35; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - MS Word 4.0, 16_36; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Laserwriter II fonts, 16_37; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - Stanford Font, MacWrite, Princeton Font, 16_38; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - TEX 1.01, 16_39; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - TEX 1.2, 1990 Mar; 16_40; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - TEX misc. stuff, 1989 Sep 21; 16_41; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - LATEX, 16_42; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)
    - TEX MACROS as supploed by Mr. Clarke to me gratis, 1988 Aug; 16_43; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 16)